Chandni Nigam

Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh | +918787095139 | nigamchandni139@gmail.com

Github | LinkedIn | https://chandninigam.com

Summary

I am a passionate and quick-learning software engineer with around 2+ years of professional experience in developing frontend systems with vanilla javascript and typescript. I am skilled in and use React, React Native, Next.js, Redux to develop web and mobile applications.

Work Experience

Software Engineer, Okoders

April 2023 - Feb 2024

- Worked on UK based fashion ecommerce application built using React Native.
- Worked on Delhi Government's SewaBharti application built using React Native.

Software Engineer, Jaxl Innovations

June 2021 - Dec 2022

- Worked on different frontend modules, using Vanilla JS/TS and maintained reusable and scalable components.
- Maintained modular architecture using npm.

Projects

Web Playgrounds (React) https://web-playgrounds.netlify.app/

- Created an IDE for HTML, CSS and JS using React.js
- Used React Context for global state management.

Instagram Clone (React Native) https://github.com/chandninigam/Insta-ui

- Built the Instagram UI clone using React Native.
- Used React Native's Dimension API for responsive UI

Skills

Languages: Javascript, Typescript

Web: HTML, CSS/SCSS, React, Next.js

Mobile: React Native Testing: Mocha, Chai

Version Control: Git

Education

Babu Banarasi Das: National Institute of Technology and Management

CGPA: 8.0

B. Tech - Computer Science (2017-2021)